sale-wow.co.uk 2014-11-02

# sale-wow.co.uk - Price Comparison, test reports and product ratings on sale-wow.co.uk. Find the best prices now! - Legal

iKee GmbH  
Nelkenweg 8  
87493 Lauben  
Germany

E-Mail: info@xxl-sale.co.uk   
Phone: +49 (0)89 / 381 5702-1

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

Our website uses cookies. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

**(1) Credit**

This document was created using an [SEQ Legal](http://www.seqlegal.com/free-legal-documents/privacy-policy) template.

**(2) What information do we collect**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation

(b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters

(c) any other information that you choose to send to us

**(3) Cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; keep track of items in your shopping basket; prevent fraud and increase website security. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit and keep track of your preferences in relation to your use of our website.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

Our advertisers services providers may also send you cookies.

We publish Google AdSense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using the DART cookie. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer (version 9) you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block All Cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

**(4) Using your personal information**

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website

(c) enable your use of the services available on the website

(d) send you our newsletter marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (and you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)

(e) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user

(f) keep the website secure and prevent fraud

(g) verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of the website (including monitoring private messages sent through our website private messaging service)

We will not, without your express consent, provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

**(5) Security of your personal information**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall-protected) servers.

**(6) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

**(7) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(8) Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to info@xxl-sale.co.uk.

*Incl. VAT, plus delivery. Interim changes to the information are possible. Unfortunately, it is not possible for us to update all prices stated on our website in real-time. Therefore the prices may have increased since the last update and before entering into any purchase agreement, you should check with the shop that all information is up to date and correct.
